Harris Lane

4801 Roanoke Pkwy Apt 602, Kansas City, MO, 64112 * (334) 405-1789 * hglane@crimson.ua.edu

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Adaptable professional with 3 years of experience in various financial roles with proven knowledge of consumer and commercial financing, financial institution relations, and consultative sales. Aiming to leverage my skills to successfully broaden involvement with financial data analytics.

SKILLS AND EXPERTISE

Credit Analyzation | Budget Forecasting | Visual Sales Demonstration | State & Federal Finance Regulation Lending & Banking Relations | Loan Approval Oversight | Advanced Microsoft Excel | Marketing

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

COMMERCE BANK, Kansas City, MO

Commercial Loan Servicing Representative, May 2019 - Present

- Initiated UCC filings for all branches within the bank's network
- Collaborated with loan officers to ensure appropriate loan documentation was recorded
- Created records for use of monitoring commercial collateral (Real Estate, UCC, Vehicles, etc.)
- Colluded with various state and county departments to file appropriate collateral security interests

STRATEGIC CAPITAL, Overland Park, KS

Capital Advisor, Feb 2019 - May 2019

- Provided potential clients with directional information regarding financial products and services
- Analyzed business banking statements and qualified clients for tailored financial instruments
- Established relationships between lending institutions and clients
- Made 100+ outbound cold calls to prospecting clients each day

AUTOALERT, Kansas City, MO

Sales Development Associate, Sep 2018 - Feb 2019

- Initiated marketing and lead generating activities in accordance with policies and procedures
- Completed and recorded all information regarding lead generation activities in the company CRM
- Reviewed and completed legal documentation with General Managers and Dealer Principals
- Made 100+ outbound cold calls to prospecting dealerships each day

JOE MACHENS AUTO DEALERSHIPS, Columbia, MO

Finance Manager, Jan 2018 - Jul 2018

- Prepared and communicated federal and state loan documents for automobile purchases
- Generated a profit of over \$85,000 through sales of finance and insurance products for Q1, 2018
- Served as the last leg of an automobile purchase to ensure that each sale and loan could be finalized within legal regulation

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF KANSAS EDWARDS CAMPUS

Overland Park, MO

Completed coursework towards Coding Bootcamp Full Stack Web Development (Feb 2020)

THE UNIVERSITY OF ALABAMA

Tuscaloosa, AL

B.S. Finance (May 2016)